Mss.Rec.99 Mss.Rec.99
American Philosophical Society
Yavapai language material
1974
Mss.Rec.99
American Philosophical Society
3.0 Reel(s)
Linguistic field recordings recorded in Prescott, Arizona, June - August 1974. Elicitation of Yavapai vocabulary and grammar. Also includes stories and speech given in Yavapai only.
3 sound cassette (55 min.): analog, 1 7/8 ips, stereo
Simoncsics, Peter
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Peter Simoncsics in 1974 (Acc. 1974 945rec). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Sound recordings; Yavapai language
- Audio recordings
  - Yavapai words and sentences, 1974-06-27; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:08:17; Mitchell, Mrs.; Simoncsics, Peter
    Scope and Contents note
    First 1:41 contains some sound distortion.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Audiocassette) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Prescott (Ariz.); Yavapai language
  - Yavapai numbers and sentences, 1974-06-28; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:31; Mitchell, Mrs.; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai pronouns and sentences, 1974-07-03; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:44; Mitchell, Mrs.; Simoncsics, Peter
    Primarily consists of variations of the sentence "X see(s) Y".
  - Yavapai possessives, 1974-07-08; 01-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:28; Mitchell, Mrs.; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-07-08; 01-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:09; Simoncsics, Peter
    Speaker not identified in collector's documentation.
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-07-12; 01-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:24; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Interview with Yavapai children, 1974-07-12; 01-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:39; Hunter, Albert; Mitchell, Eddie; Mitchell, Mrs.; Simoncsics, Peter; Ulva, Laurie
    Prescott (Ariz.); Yavapai Indians
  - Yavapai possessives, 1974-07-12; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:29; Simoncsics, Peter
    Yavapai speaker not identified in collector's documentation.
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-07-18; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:13; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai sentences, 1974-07-25; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:57; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-07; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:42; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-07-31; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:43; Simoncsics, Peter
  - Yavapai speech, 1974-08-01; 03-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:03; Simoncsics, Peter